upsi.edu.my 2019-12-22

# Policy & Disclaimer – UPSI | Portal Rasmi Universiti Pendidikan Sultan Idris

#### **Data Protection**

The latest technology includes data encryption to protect data and compliance to strict security standards are maintained to prevent unauthorised access. 

#### **Storage Security**

All electronic storage and personal data transaction are protected and stored using appropriate security technology.

 **Your Privacy** This page explains our privacy policy which includes the use and protection of any information submitted by visitors. If you choose to make any transaction or send an e-mail which contains  personal information, this information may be shared where necessary with other Government agencies so as to serve you in the most efficient and effective manner. An example might be in terms of resolving or addressing complaints that require escalation to other Government agencies. **Information Collected** No personal information will be gathered while you are using this website except for information given via e-mail. **What Happens When I Link to Another Site?** This web site contains links to other websites. This privacy policy applies only to our site and you should be aware that other sites linked by this web site may have different privacy policies and we highly recommend that you read and understand the privacy statements of each site. ** ** **Policy Amendments** If this privacy policy changes in any way, it will be updated on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are updated on the collected information, how it is used and under what circumstances, if any, it is shared with other parties.

The Government of Malaysia is not liable for any loss or damage caused by the usage of any information obtained from this web site.
